(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-03T05:51:38.246070",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
夢ってなんだろう
What is a dream...
上手く言えない私へ
to someone like me who can't put it into words,
歌っていいんだよ
you can sing,
眩しい光の中で
within the dazzling light.
恥ずかしくって俯いちゃう私へ
To someone like me who gets shy and looks down,
泣いていいんだよ
you can cry,
ちゃんと伝えたいなら
if you truly want to convey it.
孤独は消えないよ
Loneliness won't disappear,
肩を寄せ合うんだよ
but we lean on each other's shoulders.
さみしいよ 愛しいよ
I'm lonely, I love you,
大丈夫 大丈夫
it's okay, it's okay.
それが私のストーリー
That's my story,
風に迷い笑うひとひら
a single petal drifting and smiling in the wind.
諦めかけた分だけ 繋がり合える手のひら
Palms that can connect just as much as I almost gave up.
それは色鮮やかで 目まぐるしくて綺麗で
It's so colorful, dazzling, and beautiful,
「夢みたいだね」ってさ きっとキミも思うでしょ
saying "It's like a dream," I'm sure you think so too.
みんな！みこの生誕ライブ
Everyone! Miko's birthday live
2025に来てくれてありがとー！
thank you for coming in 2025!
盛り上がっていくぞー！
Let's get hyped up!
ねぇねぇあのねコネコちゃん みんな友達
Hey hey, you know, kitty cats, everyone's friends,
夢に見たカタチ 手に入ってマジ！？
the shape we dreamed of, we really got it?!
それはすなわち 築いてきた話
That means, a story we've built up,
いろんな私 超見て欲しい！
I want you to see all kinds of me!
エリートあいさつ！ みんなにゃはろー！
Elite greeting! Nyahallo to everyone!
エリートスマイル！ ふふふきゅんっ☆
Elite smile! Hehehe kyun☆
エリートダンス！ みーみーみこみこっ！
Elite dance! Mi-mi-miko-miko!
エリートイングリッシュ！ I'll be back!
Elite English! I'll be back!
まあね時にはね 落ち込んじゃうこともあるよ
Well, sometimes I get down too,
そんな時は はなまるあげるね
at times like that, I'll give you a passing grade!
お前らよく聞けーーー！！！
You guys, listen up well—!!!
みこのメドレー いっくぞー！
Miko's medley, let's go!
にゃってにゃってにゃって混ぜたら キュンしちゃうからみこチューン
If you mix nyatte nyatte nyatte, it'll make you kyunded, Miko Tune!
ぱにゃってぽにってぽよったら 一緒にせーの！ドキドキめめのきゅん！
If you panyatte, ponitte, poyottara, together ready, dokidoki meme no kyun!
ぽこぽこめめめめろきゅん？
Pokopoko memememerokyun?
きらきらめめめめろきゅん！ きゅんきゅん！
Kirakira memememerokyun! Kyun kyun!
キュンにきゅんを あげるよ
I'll give you kyun on top of kyun!
What time is it now? 11:35!
Say Japanese! 1135!
まあ1人でいると考えてっちゃうな
Well, when I'm alone, I start overthinking,
自信と不安で サンドイッチ
a sandwich of confidence and anxiety.
わかんなくなってきちゃった
I started not understanding anything,
みこかわいい？超かわいい！ 間違ってないのだ君がいる
Miko cute? Super cute! There's no mistake since you're here.
だよねぇ？（みこちはエリート！） ほんとに？（ほんとにエリート！） がんばれ！（みこちはエリート！）
Right? (Mikochi is elite!) Really? (Really elite!) Do your best! (Mikochi is elite!)
みこちゃんに応援されてるよ
You're cheering for Miko!
冗談好きなクセに 毎分毎秒わがちか あっちいね楽しいね
Despite loving jokes, every minute and second... it's hot, it's fun!
本気で想い合って そのくせバカばっか言い合って
Caring for each other seriously, yet saying stupid things to each other,
好き勝手やってんね でも今日くらいは
doing whatever we want, but today at least,
ちゃんと聞いててね？ 控えめに言って神
listen carefully, okay? To put it mildly, you're god-tier.
伝えたい愛 朝も夜も胸いっぱいさ くらくらしちゃってたまらないの
Love I want to convey, morning and night my heart is full, dizzy and irresistible!
純度100%で 大好きだ！
100% purity, I love you!
ギュッてギュッてチャームing 全世界共通 ラブあんどピース
Hug and hug, charming, universal across the whole world, love and peace!
きっとお似合いだよ ユーあんどミー
We're surely a match, you and me,
このまま二人で なんちゃってー！
just like this, the two of us... just kidding!
君に今ただ届けたい 他にはないアミューズメント
I just want to deliver this to you right now, an amusement unlike any other,
「いいみこ」って届けて毎日 目を合わせたら笑ってくれる
delivering "Good Miko" every day, when our eyes meet you smile for me.
当たり前のような奇跡 もらうばかりじゃいんない 今ここで恩返し
A miracle that feels so ordinary, can't just keep receiving, now here I'll repay you!
ずっと見ててよね？ 控えめに言って神 伝えたい愛
Keep watching me, okay? To put it mildly, god-tier, love I want to convey,
朝も夜も胸いっぱいさ くらくらしちゃってたまらないの
morning and night my heart is full, dizzy and irresistible!
純度100%で 大好きだ！
100% purity, I love you!
ギュッてギュッてチャームing 全世界共通 ラブあんどピース
Hug and hug, charming, universal across the whole world, love and peace!
きっとお似合いだよ ユーあんどミー 飽きるほど一杯
We're surely a match, you and me, a cup to the brim until we're tired,
隣で歌うよ このまま二人で なんちゃってー！
singing right beside you, just like this the two of us... just kidding!
にゃっはろーわーるど！！！ さあ行こう！！！
Nyahallo World!!! Let's go!!!
エリート舐めんな！ 独壇場（はいっ！）
Don't underestimate elite! A one-person show!
配信だ！今日手も集まれー！！！ 箱庭で愛を！！！
It's a stream! Gather today too—!!! Love in a miniature garden!
にゃっはろーわーるど！！！
Nyahallo World!!!
さあ行こう！！！
Here we go!!!
セミコピで掲げろ
Hold it up high!
配信だ！配信だ！きみに！きみが！
It's a stream! To you! You are—
乳酸菌なんて！！！
Lactic acid bacteria or something?!
にゃっはろーわーるど！！！
Nyahallo World!!!
さあ行こう！！！
Here we go!!!
セミコピで掲げろ
Hold it up high!
配信だ！配信だ！わーつーで！
It's a stream! One, two, day!
想い出詰まったロケットは
A rocket packed with memories
水がなくたって飛べるから！！！
can fly even without water!!!
光ってほら、虹色だね
Shining, look, it's rainbow colored.
ひとりずつ名前呼ぶよ
I'll call out your names one by one.
わんつーさんし！
One, two, three, four!
きみとのいもの探して
Searching for things with you,
おひめさまみていた
I was looking at you like a princess.
あーゆーでぃー！
Are you ready?!
至ってはちゃちゃな
Reaching utter absurdity,
めちゃめちゃ風なLADY
acting like a total lady.
壊してサヨナラ　下向きなセンス
Destroy it and say goodbye to downward-looking sense.
あーゆーでぃー！
Are you ready?!
至ってはちゃちゃな　めちゃめちゃ風なLADY
Reaching utter absurdity, acting like a total lady.
歌して麗らか　さくらカモンベイビー
Singing brightly, Sakura come on baby!
ねえだって後には引けないもん
Hey, because I can't back down now!
あすにだってだって負くんないよね
Tomorrow as well, I won't lose, right?!
ねえもうやだやだミスってなんない
Hey, no more, no more, I won't make mistakes!
もうやだやだ踊ってベイビダンス
No more, no more, dance, baby dance!
あたしはまだ諦めない　でも　でも　全然だめかも
I still won't give up, but... maybe I'm hopeless.
だってベイビダンス　うまくできないの
Because, baby dance, I can't do it well.
伝えられないの　もっと可愛くなりたいのに
I can't convey it, even though I want to be cuter.
どうしたらいいとかわかんないし
I don't even know what I should do.
まだ　まだ　いけるかな
Can I still, still keep going?
まだ　まだ　言えるかな
Can I still, still say it?
まだ　まだ　できるかな
Can I still, still do it?
まだ　まだ…ううん、さあ進め！
Still... No, come on, let's go!
ポンコツでドジでダメで足りないことばっかだって　きっとやめないんだ
Clumsy, hopeless, and lacking—I'll never stop!
ポンコツでドジでダメで足りないことばっかだって　見ていてほしい
Clumsy, hopeless, and lacking—watch me!
ねえもうやだやだミスってなんない
Hey, no more, no more, I won't make mistakes!
もうやだやだ踊ってベイビダンス
No more, no more, dance, baby dance!
あたしはまだ諦めない　ほら　ほら　全然だめじゃない
I still won't give up! Look, I'm not hopeless!
だってベイビダンス　きみに届くまで
Because, baby dance, until it reaches you,
だってベイビダンス　きみに会えるまで
because, baby dance, until I can meet you.
もっと可愛くなりたいからどんな時だってそう頑張れるし
Because I want to be cuter, I can always work hard.
やだやだミスってなんないね？
No more, no more, don't make mistakes, okay?
前向けぐんぐん　しゅぱつ進行
Looking straight ahead, full speed, departure ahead!
立ち止まる予定あるわけない
There's no way I plan on stopping.
笑顔にさせちゃう　かみさま信仰
I'll make you smile, faith in god!
それつまりどこどのどきらさま？
That is, which, which sparkly-sama?
さあ始めようか　空を染め上げて
Now then, shall we begin? Dyeing the sky,
ほらあっちもこっちもどっちもにっちもそっちも華やかに変えてゆこうよ！
look everywhere, let's change it gorgeously!
さくらひらり時は来たり　甘く昂るように
Blossoms flutter, the time has come, sweetly surging,
きらりきらり輝くから　信じてついてきてね！
shining sparklingly, believe in me and follow!
さくらひらり夢を見たり　どんな困難だって
Blossoms flutter, dreaming, no matter what happens,
きみと二人乗り越えるよ　うまずたゆまずさあススメ！
we'll overcome it together, now let's advance!
かじかむ冬にたったひとり
In the numbing winter, all alone,
枝の先膨らんでいたつぼみ
a bud swelling at the tip of the branch
春の風を待ってたんだよ
was waiting for the spring breeze.
それはキミという風　背中を押すまぶしいパワー
That's the wind called you, a dazzling power!
さくらひらり時は来たり　甘く昂るように
Blossoms flutter, the time has come, sweetly surging,
きらりきらり輝くから　信じてついてきてね！
shining sparklingly, believe in me and follow!
さくらひらり夢を見たり　どんな困難だって
Blossoms flutter, dreaming, no matter what happens,
きみと二人乗り越えるよ　うまずたゆまずさあススメ！
we'll overcome it together, now let's advance!
うまずたゆまずさあススメ！
Steadily, now let's advance!
みんなにゃっはろー！
Everyone, nyahallo!
精英巫女アイドルさくらみこです！
Elite Miko idol Sakura Miko here!
え、さくらみこ生誕祭2025！
Sakura Miko Birthday Festival 2025!
りめんばーからずに来てくれてどうもありがとう！
Thank you so much for coming without missing it!
え、今回のハッシュ…
Um, this time's hash...
次はさくらみこ生誕祭。こちらですね。
Next up is Sakura Miko's birthday festival, right here!
え、写真感想をたくさんポストしてくれると嬉しいです。
I'd be so happy if you posted lots of photo impressions!
はあ、と、いうことでね、1曲目はさくらみこオリジナル曲メドレーでした！
And so, the first song was a Sakura Miko original song medley!
ソロライブではね、歌えなかったオリジナル曲も歌いたくてメドレーやってみようかって軽い気持ちでやったらね、大変なことになりました。
In my solo live, I wanted to sing original songs I couldn't perform, and it turned into a huge ordeal.
はい、どうでしたか？みんなよかったかな？
Yeah, how was it? Was it good, everyone?
アルバムもね、たくさんみんな聞いててくださいね！
Please keep listening to the album a lot, everyone!
え、今回のコンセプトは、お姫様のとおり…お姫様のとおり、お姫様、お姫様、となっております。
Um, the concept this time is, as you heard... as you heard, Princess, Princess.
え、そして、去年のソロライブの感謝も込めたライブとなっております！みんなたくさん本当にいつもありがとう！うわあ！
And it's a live show filled with gratitude for last year's solo live! Thank you all so much, always! Whoa!
え、聞いてください。
Um, please listen.
一緒は、ソロライブでお披露目したドレス、見て！かわいい！
Together, the dress I unveiled at my solo live, look! So cute!
靴もね、あの靴、靴見える？あ、靴もね、こちらガラスの靴になってるんだよ。シンデレラですね。
And the shoes too, can you see them? Ah, they're glass slippers. Like Cinderella.
そして、あの色もね、本当はですね、ソロライブではピンクのね、ドレスをたくさん着てたんですが、今回は白のドレスでやっていきたいと思います。かわいい！かわいい！
Actually, at the solo live I wore lots of pink dresses, but this time I want to do it in a white dress. Cute! Cute!
え、あ、このステージだ。ステージもね、さくらの「お姫様」のコンセプトで作ってもらいました！
The stage too, was made with Sakura's "Princess" concept!
すごい！うわ、すご！カメラ見えてる！いやあ、素敵ですね。
Amazing! Wow, amazing! The camera can see it! Oh, how wonderful.
豪華になりましたね。この後もいろんなね、演出があるかもしれないのでお楽しみ！
It became so grand. There might be various productions after this too, so look forward to it!
そして、最後には告知もありますので、最後まで絶対見てね！
And finally, there will be announcements too, so be sure to watch until the end!
それでは、ゲストパート行くぞ！
Now then, let's go to the guest part!
だっだっだ 大丈夫じゃない
Don't-don't-don't you know it's not alright
ちょっと繭になって出直すわわわ
I'll retreat back into my cocoon and hit rewind...
愛とか恋とか全部くだらない がっかりするだけダメを知るだけ
Don't care for love, crushes don't mean a thing, all I can see is the pain that they guarantee.
あたし馬鹿ね ダサい逆走じゃん
I'm running in the wrong direction like a moron.
ホントのところはあなたにモテたい 失敗するのにビビってるだけ
Fact is, attraction to you is causing thoughts of a possible awful ending...
加工なしの厳しめの条件じゃ
Since I can't hide behind a filter right before your eyes.
ちょっと こんな時 どんな顔すればいいか教えてほしい
Hold on, all I need to know is how to hold my own with you, so tell me please.
ちょっと 「愛してる」だとかそんな言葉で壊れてみたい
Hold on, all I wanna do when I hear the words "I love you" is to go insane!
じれったいな
I've had enough!
ハロー 残念なあたし
Hello once again unlucky me!
困っちゃって イアイア
I can't understand or stand it!
じれったいな 決まんないの前髪が 怒っちゃって イライラ
I've had enough! I can't get my hair to play along, unbearably irritating!
だっだっだ 大好きは もっと可愛くなって言いたいのに
I-i-i wanna say I'm in love, but I wanna save those words for when I'm cute enough.
だっだっだ 大丈夫じゃない
Don't-don-don't you know it's not alright.
ちょっと繭になって出直すわわわ
I'll retreat back into my cocoon and hit rewind...
あ… えと、いや…なんでもない 言いたいこと言えたことないや
Uh, you know, really, just pay me no mind, don't have the courage to say what I desire.
目と目止められないの 逸らしちゃってまた自己嫌悪
Try to pry my eyes from diverting my deep rooted hate for myself, deep down inside, oh.
じれったいな ハロー 残念なあたし
I've had enough! Hello once again unlucky me!
困っちゃって イアイア
I can't understand or stand it!
じれったいな 入んないのこの靴が
I've had enough! I can't get these crystal slippers on,
怒っちゃって イライラ 鐘が鳴って 灰になって
unbearably irritating! The bell is ringing the ash is raining.
あたし まだ帰りたくないや XXコースへ
I don't think that I am ready to be leaving the course that's labelled "x".
飛び込んでみたいから
I want to try diving into it!
じれったいな ハロー 残念なあたし
I've had enough! Hello once again unlucky me!
困っちゃって イアイア
I can't understand or stand it!
じれったいな 決まんないの前髪が
I've had enough! I can't get my hair to play along,
怒っちゃってる じれったいな
it's driving me mad! I've had enough!
夜行前のシンデレラ ビビっちゃって フラフラ
The first time for Cinderella, so scared that my head is spinning.
ハローをくれたあなたと 踊っちゃって クラクラ
From when we first danced and you said hello, you've had me in circles, spinning.
だっだっだ 大好きは もっと可愛くなって言いたいのに
I-i-i wanna say I'm in love, but I wanna save those words for when I'm cute enough.
だっだっだ 大丈夫じゃない
Don't-don-don't you know it's not alright.
ちょっとお待たせになって 王子様
Won't you wait for me, my charming prince in shining armour.
だっだっだ ダメよ順序とか もっと仲良くなってそうじゃない？
I-i-i wanna wait just a bit, let's explore a little more before we carry on.
だっだっだ マジで大丈夫じゃない やっぱ繭になって出直すわ
Don't-don-don't you know I'm not alright, I'll retreat back into my cocoon and hit rewind.
だくだくだく 大丈夫じゃない
Dadakudaku, not alright,
ちょっと蛹になって出直すわ
I'll turn into a pupa and start over.
白い雪のプリンセスは
[Song: Shiroi Yuki no Princess]
鏡よ鏡よ鏡さん
Mirror, mirror, on the wall,
世界で一番可愛いのは私？
Who is the cutest in the world?
なんてやっと毛のような視線迫る
Gazes closing in on me like hair...
優しいフリした彼女が素敵な晩餐もてなした
A seemingly kind girl hosted a wonderful banquet,
そっと口に含むと
and when I softly took it in my mouth,
薄れゆく意識の中で
Fading within my consciousness,
夢を見る いつかのおとぎ話
I dream of a fairytale from long ago.
時が止まる
Time stops.
お願いKISSで目を覚まして欲しいの
I want you to wake me with a kiss, please.
白い棺から連れ出すように
As if leading me out of a white coffin.
突き刺す憎しみはドラマ的な事情 祈っても
Piercing hatred is a dramatic circumstance, even if I pray,
君はまだ来ない
you still don't come.
鏡よ鏡よ鏡さん
Mirror, mirror, on the wall,
ネクタイまかせほぼに挨拶するから
Entrusting my tie, I give a casual greeting,
嫉妬を買われてしまった
and ended up drawing jealousy.
7人の小人はいるけど
The seven dwarfs are here, but
助ける素振り知らんふりね そっと首を掴まれ
pretending not to notice and not helping, gently grabbing my neck...
一粒の涙さえも
Even a single teardrop
拭えなくて 呼吸もままならない
cannot be wiped away, and breathing is impossible.
視界失せ消えそうだから 早く駆けて欲しいの
My vision is fading away, so I want you to run to me quickly.
訳は聞かないで 答えられない
Don't ask me why, I can't answer.
望まない 憎まれは深い愛の二乗
Unwanted hatred is the square of deep love,
もうすぐでいなくなるのかな
wondering if I'll disappear soon.
鏡よ鏡よ鏡さん
Mirror, mirror, on the wall,
途切れてく命の音を
The fading sound of life,
毒リンゴを食いに少女のように眠りにつく
falling asleep like a girl eating a poisoned apple.
お願いKISSで目を覚まして欲しいの
I want you to wake me with a kiss, please.
胸の中の声 届きますか
Can you hear the voice inside my chest?
階段を上ったらドアを開けるだけで見つかるよ
If you climb the stairs, just opening the door will lead you to me.
お願いKISSで目を覚まして欲しいの
I want you to wake me with a kiss, please.
白い棺から連れ出すように
As if leading me out of a white coffin.
突き刺す憎しみはドラマ的な事情 祈っても君はまだ来ない
Piercing hatred is a dramatic circumstance, yet even if I pray, you still don't come.
消えてしまうその前に
Before I disappear...
わがままプリンセス
[Song: Wagamama Princess]
思い通りにいかない 籠の鳥のまま自由を望んでいるの
Unable to have things my way, I yearn for freedom like a bird in a cage.
一生私のそばに居てね
Stay by my side forever.
誓えますか？ここにサインして！ (yeah)
Can you swear? Sign right here! (Yeah)
忘れられない思い出を
Memories we can never forget,
これからたくさん作ろう イェイ イェイ イェイ！
let's make plenty of them from now on, yay yay yay!
恥ずかしそうに来てくれるけど
You come over looking so shy, but
キミの好きなところを脳内検索中
I'm searching my brain for the things you like.
感じたまま口に出せば照れ笑いして
Expressing how I feel makes you smile shyly,
とても可愛すぎる ダイ・ダイ・ダイスキ！
and you're far too cute—so, so, so much!
超キュートなワタシを見て？目を離しちゃダメじゃん (ダメじゃん)
Look at super-cute me? Don't look away! (Don't look away)
誰が一番カワイイかって？決まってるでしょ！ジョ・ウ・シキ！
Who's the cutest of all? Obviously me! That's common sense!
今日からもっと素直になってスキを伝えて！ (スキスキスキスキスキ)
Starting today, be more honest and tell me you love me! (Love love love love love)
キミのハートをゲットー (ゲットー)
I'll capture your heart! (Capture it!)
逃さないように カ・ク・ホ！
Securing you so you can't escape!
いつでも独り占めできる気分は最高！
Being able to hog you all to myself feels amazing!
なんでもわがまま聞いてくれるキミに夢中 I LOVE YOU (yeah)
I'm crazy about you for granting my every whim, I love you! (Yeah)
一生私のそばに居てね
Stay by my side forever.
誓えますか？ここにサインして！ (yeah)
Can you swear? Sign right here! (Yeah)
こんなにも可愛い私を
Such a cute girl like me—
一人にはしないでね (ほら！)
don't leave me all alone! (Hey!)
喧嘩することもあるかも？
We might argue sometimes,
それでも好きでいてくれるよね？ (絶対！)
but you'll still love me, right? (Definitely!)
忘れられない思い出を
Memories we can never forget,
これからたくさん作ろう イェイ イェイ イェイ！
let's make plenty of them from now on, yay yay yay!
特別な日に気分“超”ローテンション
On a special day, you're in super low spirits.
君は忘れてたよね
You completely forgot, didn't you?
間抜な顔でごめんて
With that silly face, saying "sorry."
言い訳なんか聞きたくない 勘弁して
I don't want to hear any excuses, spare me.
もう信じられないよ ダイ・ダイ・ダイキライ！
I can't trust you anymore—I hate, hate, hate you!
何が悪いかわかってんの？ほら、言ってみ？言ってみ？言えないじゃん！？
Do you even know what's wrong? Come on, say it! Say it! You can't, can you!?
もうどうしていつもそうなの？1ミリたりとも誠意感じない (最悪ー)
Why are you always like this? I don't feel a shred of sincerity. (The worst)
不真面目トーク 怒りはピーク お仕置きだよ (ビシビシビシビシ)
Insincere talk, my anger has peaked, time for punishment! (Smack smack smack smack)
次は無い これが最後よ 夢中になってくれなきゃダメよ！
There's no next time, this is the last chance. You gotta be obsessed with me!
嘘はない 真実はただ一つ
There are no lies, the truth is only one.
私だけの… 見つけちゃった♥
I found... my very own♥
世界中どこ探してもキミみたいに素敵な人はいない！ (いない！)
Search the whole world over, there's no one as wonderful as you! (No one!)
二人ならなんでもできる
If we're together, we can do anything.
LOVEパワー大爆発 ドッカーン！
Love power massive explosion, ka-boom!
毎日笑いあって生きよう
Let's live laughing together every day,
たくさんの笑顔で朝から超happy！
super happy from the morning with lots of smiles!
特別な時間（とき）が待ってる
A special time is waiting for us,
手を繋いでどこまでも イェイ イェイ イェイ！
holding hands anywhere we go, yay yay yay!
何度だってキミに好きを伝えよう
I'll tell you I love you no matter how many times,
嫌いになんかならないでよね
so don't ever start hating me, okay?
最大級の愛を心から送ろう
I'll send you my greatest love from the bottom of my heart,
いつまでもずっと イェーイ！
forever and ever, yeah!
一生私のそばに居てね
Stay by my side forever.
誓えますか？ここにサインして！
Can you swear? Sign right here!
こんなにも可愛い私を
Such a cute girl like me—
一人にはしないでね！ せーの！ LOVE YOU！
don't leave me all alone! Ready, set! Love you!
喧嘩することもあるかも？
We might argue sometimes,
それでも好きでいてくれるよね？ (絶対！)
but you'll still love me, right? (Definitely!)
忘れられない思い出を
Memories we can never forget,
これからたくさん作ろう イェイ イェイ イェイ！
let's make plenty of them from now on, yay yay yay!
ワンワンワンワン イェイイェイイェイイェイ...
Woof woof woof woof, yay yay yay yay...
今なんじゃない？メラメラとたぎる
Isn't it now? Blazing passionately,
眠っているだけの正義
justice that's just lying dormant.
こんな僕も君のヒーローになりたいのさ
Even a guy like me wants to be your hero!
かっこいい君には僕じゃ頼りないのかなんて
Wondering if someone as cool as you is too good for someone like me—
そりゃそうだよなってだって今こうして迷ってる
Well of course you'd think that, since I'm hesitating right now.
手を取ってくれないか 君が僕のヒーローだったように
Won't you take my hand, just like you were my hero?
君が僕のヒーローだったように
Just like you were my hero.
今なんじゃない？メラメラとたぎる
Isn't it now? Blazing passionately,
こんな僕にも潜む正義がどうしようもない衝動に駆られて
the justice hidden even inside me is driven by an unstoppable impulse!
ほら
Hey...
ほら気付けば手を握っている
Look, before you know it, we're holding hands.
いったいぜんたい
Just what in the world...
そんなに荷物を背負い込んでどこへ行くの
Are you carrying so much luggage to where?
ねえねえ待って
Hey, hey, wait...
僕にちょっと預けてみては
Why don't you leave a little with me?
信じてばかりの僕と
With me who only believes,
信じることが怖い君と
And you who are afraid to believe,
どちらが正しいのかなんて
Which one is right?
誰にも分からないさ
Nobody knows.
僕らだけの世界
A world that's just the two of us,
ギブとテイクさ
Give and take.
補い合えた暁には同じ夢を見たい
I want to see the same dream in the dawn we make up for each other.
君はかっこいいと苦しめて
You're cool, and you suffer,
ひとりぼっちにさせたのは
And leaving you all alone...
少し僕のせいなんだよねごめんね
Is a little my fault, sorry.
だけど見るべきはリアルだ
But what we should look at is the real.
今こそ僕が救えるんだ
Now is the time I can save you.
抱えないで信じて頼って欲しいんだ
Don't hold it in, believe in me, rely on me.
今なんじゃない? メラメラとたぎる
What is it now? Mela mela and sparkling,
こんな僕にも潜む正義が
Justice lurking even inside someone like me,
どうしようもない衝動に駆られて
Driven by an overwhelming impulse,
ほら気付けば手を握っている
Look, before you know it, we're holding hands.
ほっとけない
Can't leave you be!
そんなに荷物を背負い込んでどこへ行くの
Are you carrying so much luggage to where?
ほんのちょっと僕にちょっと預けてみては
Why don't you leave a little with me?
こんな僕も君のヒーローになりたいのさ
I want to be your hero too.
できっこないを やなくちゃ
You gotta do the impossible!
どんなに打ちのめされたって悲しみに心を任せちゃだめだよ
Don't let sadness take over your heart no matter how beaten down you are.
君は今逃げたいっていうけど
You say you want to run away right now,
それが本音なのかい?
Is that really how you feel?
僕にはそうは思えないよ
I just can't see it that way.
何も実らなかったなんて悲しい言葉だよ
"Nothing ever came of it" -- what a sad thing to say.
心を少しでも不安にさせちゃだめさ 灯りをともそう
Don't let your heart get even a little anxious, light the fire!
あきらめないでどんな時も
Don't ever give up, no matter when!
君なら出来るんだどんな事も
If it's you, you can do anything!
今世界にひとつだけの強い力をみたよ
I saw the only powerful strength in this world!
君ならできない事だってできるんだ本当さ嘘じゃないよ
That you can do the impossible is the absolute truth!
今世界にひとつだけの強い光をみたよ
I saw the only powerful light in this world!
アイワナビーア 君の全て!
I wanna be your everything!
今年もみこも感情に言わせてくれてありがとう
Thank you for sharing your feelings with me this year too!
これからもたくさん
I'll keep giving it my all!
やはり自分じゃだめかなんて無駄な言葉だよ
Saying 'I guess I'm not good enough' is such useless words.
心を少しでも不安にさせちゃだめさ灯りをともそう
Don't let your heart become anxious; let's light up the flame.
あきらめないでどんな時も君ならできるんだどんな事も
Never give up, no matter when—you can do anything!
今世界にひとつだけの強い力をみたよ
I witnessed a strength found nowhere else in the world.
君ならできないことだってできるんだホントさ嘘じゃないよ
You can do the impossible; it's the truth, no lie.
今世界にひとつだけの強い光をみたよ
I witnessed a light found nowhere else in the world.
アイワナビーア君の全て！
I wanna be your everything!
ドキドキしてRouge？行きましょ～！
Heart pounding with Rouge? Let's go!
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！無罪！まりん！まりん！まりんも無罪！
Not guilty! Not guilty! Pretty girl not guilty!
やっぱキラキラ、もっとクラクラ！
Sparkling brighter, dizzying further!
ねぇ、言ったよね？年齢なんて関係ない、さっさとめんどくさいのも含めて愛してくれるって？
Hey, you said age doesn't matter, and that you'd love all my annoying parts?
ねぇねぇ、言ったよね？言ってない？ふーん、そう言うこと言うんだ。
Hey hey, you said it, right? You didn't? Hmph, playing that card.
ちなみにこの船では美少女無罪が適用されますけど？
By the way, on this ship, pretty girl immunity applies!
まかせて！魔法で若返り
Leave it to me! Rejuvenated by magic,
ヒミツの素顔はキミにだけ、トクベツにしょ～お？
My secret bare face is just for you—special treatment!
AH…アタシ厄介よ AH…港なんかじゃ
Ah... I'm a handful. Ah... at any port,
はしゃげないわ、近寄らないで！お宝のしまにしてほしい気分！
I can't just play around. Stay away! Make it an island of treasure!
シュッ！キュッ！ヨロレイヒ！
Swish! Snap! Yorolehi!
美少女姉妹！キミの1番目指してヨーソロー！
Pretty girl sisters! Aiming for your number one, ahoy!
本当は自信ないけど頑張っちゃう！
I'm not really confident, but I'll do my best!
キュンキュンキョンキュンキュンキュンロン！恋する気持ち中7歳！
Thumping heart, maidenly feelings at age 17!
でっぺんにネッちゃうわオトナの時間！
We're reaching the peak—it's adult time!
やっぱキラキラ、もっとクラクラ！
Sparkling brighter, dizzying further!
ドキドキしてRouge？まぁ、お許しくだたーい！
Heart pounding with Rouge? Well, please forgive me!
このマリンの魅力！魔力！不可効力！
This Marine's charm! Magic! Irresistible force!
罪な女ね！
What a sinful woman!
離さないで、つかまっていて！
Don't let go, hold on tight!
世界の広さ見せてあげるから！
I'll show you how vast the world is!
シュッ！キュッ！ヨロレイヒ！
Swish! Snap! Yorolehi!
美少女姉妹！キミの1番目指してヨーソロー！
Pretty girl sisters! Aiming for your number one, ahoy!
冗談も大好きだけど真剣よ！
I love joking around, but I'm serious!
キュンキュンキョンキュンキュンキュンロン！恋する気持ち中7歳！
Thumping heart, maidenly feelings at age 17!
でっぺんにネッちゃうわオトナの時間！
We're reaching the peak—it's adult time!
やっぱキラキラ、もっとクラクラ！
Sparkling brighter, dizzying further!
ドキドキしてRouge？まだ早い♡
Heart pounding with Rouge? Still too early♡
弱気で流したジングル
The timidly shed jingle
いつもドキドキだね第一声 (にゃっは～！)
Always pounding at the first word!
震えた声もノートの文字もみんなみんな手繋いでGO！
Shaking voices and notebook notes, everyone holding hands, go!
変わってるとねって、そうなんだ、なんて言ったの？まーいっか
You're quirky? Is that so? What did you say? Oh well.
飲み込んじゃってきた言葉も
Even the words I've swallowed down
君と笑った声でほら咲いて (ばんざい！)
Bloom with the voice of laughing with you!
こんな私でも (モーマンタイ！)
Even a me like this is totally fine!
好きだってねぇ本当？冗談？分かりそう？どっち？わかんない！本当は？
You love me? Really? Joking? Can you tell? Which is it? Who knows! Really?
さくらんぼメッセージ受け取って一せーのーせで！
Receive the cherry message all together on three!
きっともっとキュンとしちゃうようなさくらんぼメッセージ
A cherry message bound to make your heart thump even more.
つぼみにぎゅっと詰め込んで！君の前では私
Packed tightly into a bud! In front of you, I am...
愛し合う2人 幸せの空
Loving each other under a happy sky,
隣どおし あなたとあたし さくらんぼ
side by side, you and I, Sakuranbo!
誰かじゃなくて
Not just anyone,
君がいいって
I want you!
絶対!
Definitely!
何度でも言うよ
I'll say it as many times as it takes,
もう一回!
once more!
気になってね、本当?
Are you curious? Really?
ちょっとばかりそう?
Just a little bit?
わかんない! どっち?
I don't know! Which is it?
本当が!
It's the truth!
さくらんぼ メッセージ
A cherry blossom message,
受け取って
please accept it!
一生のお願いで!
It's my one lifetime request!
キュンとしちゃうよな
It makes my heart go kyunn!
さくらんぼ
Sakuranbo,
摘み実にぎゅっとつめ込んで
stuffed tight like a cherry bud,
君の前では私 らしいていていいよね
in front of you, is it okay if I'm just myself?
愛らしくいて いいよね
Is it okay to be adorable?
好きでいていいよね
Is it okay for you to love me?
ねぇ 思い出したんだ
Hey, I remembered
そっと涙した日を
the days I quietly shed tears.
さあ 数えてみようか
Come on, let's try counting
これまで起こした奇跡を
the miracles we've created so far.
ひとつ とまらない脚で
First, with unstoppable steps,
ふたつ 超えていく夢も
second, the dreams we surpass,
みっつ つながる絆は
third, the bonds that connect us—
君とひろげてきたんだよ
we've expanded them together with you.
何度でも咲くように
So that they bloom again and again,
続いてくこの物語
this story continues on.
まだ見たことのない 景色を探しに行こう
Let's go search for scenery we've never seen before!
花ひとつずつが 小さくてもほら
Even if each flower is small, see,
支え合えたら 桜になれるよ
if we support each other, we can become cherry blossoms.
ぼくらが繋いだ 大きな木はまだ
The big tree we connected together
これからも春風に乗って 伸びてくのさ
will continue to grow, riding the spring breeze from now on!
Wow...
甘くほろ苦い夢
A sweet and bittersweet dream,
これでいいか これがいいか
is this good? Is this what I want?
折れかけたあの日
On that day when I almost broke down,
ここに間違いはなくて 正解もなくて
there were no mistakes here, nor any right answers,
自分次第って 怖くて仕方ないけど
and though relying purely on myself is terrifying,
誰かじゃない "君"と見たい景色は鮮明で…
the scenery I want to see with "you", not just anyone, is vivid...
それじゃ ここで足踏みなんかしていられないじゃんっ!
So I can't just stand here marking time anymore!
無数の星の中 光は君がくれた
Amidst countless stars, you gave me this light.
もっと 超えていけるさ!
We can go even further beyond!
SUPERNOVA 起こせ、今! 何度だって翔べる
Spark a SUPERNOVA now! We can fly as many times as it takes!
これは紛れもなく僕らの軌跡
This is unmistakably our miraculous trail.
こんな現在を愛せるように
So that I can love the present moment,
君に向けて歌おう 心が叫んでる!
I'll sing out to you, my heart is crying out!
無数の星の中 光は君がくれた
Amidst countless stars, you gave me this light.
もっと 超えていけるさ!
We can go even further beyond!
SUPERNOVA 起こせ、今! 何度だって翔べる
Spark a SUPERNOVA now! We can fly as many times as it takes!
これは紛れもなく僕らの軌跡
This is unmistakably our miraculous trail.
普通も”あたりまえ”も無い 君が君らしく在れるように
With no standard or "ordinary", so that you can be truly yourself,
もっと 届けよう 不思議と怖くないんだ
let's deliver it more! Strangely, I'm not afraid anymore.
綺麗事 絵空事でもないさぁ 行こう!
It's not just sugarcoated fiction or empty words—let's go!
この物語は終わらない!
This story will never end!
Wow...
絶対アイドル辞めないで
Never stop being an idol,
輝いてる君を見たい
I want to see you shining!
もうずっとずっとずっと
Forever and ever and ever,
ステージにいて
stay on the stage!
(ooh はい！)
(Ooh, yeah!)
who a, oh-oh-oh-oh
Whoa, oh-oh-oh-oh,
who a, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh (yay!)
whoa, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh (Yay!)
私がもし君のとこ 離れたなら
If I were to ever leave your side,
君はちょっと寂しくなるかな
would you feel a little lonely?
いじわる考える
I'm having mischievous thoughts.
好きな人がいるのなら 内緒にして ねぇ
If there's someone you like, keep it secret, hey!
神様は将来と指輪を どこかに隠してね
God, please hide the future and rings somewhere!
君の「好き」に合わせたんだ髪の色
I matched my hair color to your "likes."
私の中 君だけで
Inside of me, it's only you.
過剰摂取は中毒へ
Overdose leads to addiction,
責任とってね 大好きです
take responsibility! I love you!
「せーの！」
"Ready, go!"
絶対アイドル辞めないで
Never stop being an idol,
優しい目も真面目顔も
your gentle eyes and serious face,
全部知ってる 私が言う！
I know all of it, so I am telling you!
絶対空で輝いて
Always shine in the sky,
星は街じゃ輝かないの
stars don't shine in the city streets!
眩しい君が世界一だよ
You, so dazzling, are the number one in the world!
好きだー！
(I love you!)
who a, oh-oh-oh-oh
Whoa, oh-oh-oh-oh,
who a, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh (yay!)
whoa, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh (Yay!)
君の夢は何ですか？ 教えて欲しい
What is your dream? I want you to tell me.
その夢がアイドルじゃなくても 覚悟はしてるから
Even if that dream isn't an idol, I'm already prepared.
星のいない空 それが当たり前で
A sky without stars, that was just normal,
暗い道に目が慣れずに 踏み出すのも怖かった
my eyes couldn't get used to the dark path and I was scared to take a step.
そんな時 やっと見えた光
That was when I finally saw the light.
行くぞー！
Let's go!
絶対君は歌ってて
Always keep singing,
ただのエゴとわかってても
even knowing it's just my own ego!
君はキラキラ衣装が似合う！
You look great in sparkling outfits!
絶対大きなステージで
Always on a big stage,
一列でも前で感じたい
I want to feel you closer, even in the front row.
今日の歌い方 なんか好きだなあ
I kind of like the way you sing today!
君の努力、私の愛 成り立つこの関係は
Your effort, my love, this relationship we build
強くて脆いの 星の幸せを願った
is strong yet fragile. I prayed for the star's happiness.
だけど… やめねえ！だって君はアイドルよ
But... No way! Because you are an idol!
初めて目が合った日から 今日も明日も君ばかりだ
Ever since the day our eyes first met, today and tomorrow, it's only you.
絶対アイドル辞めないで
Never stop being an idol,
これ叶わないよ おとぎ話
this is an unrequited fairy tale!
恋よりももっと好きだ
I love you even more than romance.
魔法よどうか 解けないままで
Magic, please stay unbroken!
who a, oh-oh-oh-oh
Whoa, oh-oh-oh-oh,
who a, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh (yay!)
whoa, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh (Yay!)
lu lu lu…
Lu, lu, lu...
まだ、まだ、小さな蕾だったあの頃
Back then, I was still just a small bud,
冷たい風に震えていたあの頃
shivering in the cold wind.
誰もが静かに通り過ぎていく日々
Days when everyone passed by so quietly,
立ち止まって そっと、微笑んでくれた
you stopped and gently smiled at me.
鏡を覗いたって 写真に収めたって
Whether I looked in the mirror or captured it in a photo,
ホントの色なんて ずっと、わからないまま
I never really knew my true colors.
遠くで咲き誇った キレイな花のように
Like a beautiful flower blooming far away...
まだ、まだ、小さな蕾だったあの頃
Back then, when I was still just a small bud,
冷たい風に震えていたあの頃
Shivering in the cold wind,
誰かが静かに通り過ぎていく日々
Days when everyone quietly passes by,
立ち止まってそっと、微笑んでくれた
You stopped and gently smiled at me.
鏡を覗いたって写真に収めたって
Even if I look in the mirror or capture it in a photo,
ホントの色なんてずっと、わからないまま
I still never truly knew my real color.
遠くで咲き誇ったキレイな花のように
Like a beautiful flower blooming in the distance,
なりたくてなれなくて春を待っていた
Wishing I could be like that, yet unable to, I awaited spring.
君の瞳の中 反射した私を見て
Looking at myself reflected in your eyes,
はじめて自分の色を知れたんだ
For the first time, I came to know my own color.
まだ、満開じゃないけど
Even though it's not in full bloom yet,
鮮やかな夢を映し出せるよ
I can reflect vivid dreams.
そこに君がいてくれたから
Because you were there with me.
la la la…
La la la...
どれだけ自分をキレイに描いても
No matter how beautifully I portray myself,
どれだけ自分を大きく描いても
No matter how grandly I portray myself,
君の目に映る私はいつもと同じように
To your eyes, I appear just as I always am,
不器用すぎて凸凹で でも、嫌いじゃなくて
Too clumsy, full of rough edges, but I don't hate it.
花が咲いた夢を見てた
I was dreaming of a flower blooming,
きっと、いつか触れてみたいな
Hoping that someday I might touch it.
花が咲いた夢を見てた
I was dreaming of a flower blooming,
ずっと、ずっと春を待っていた
Forever and ever, waiting for spring.
曇り空の下 涙に遮られて
Beneath cloudy skies, blocked by tears,
光が届かないときでも
Even at times when the light cannot reach,
昨日と変わらずに 明日に芽を伸ばしていこう
Just like yesterday, let's keep growing our buds toward tomorrow.
だって、Reflection
Because, it's Reflection.
そこに君がいてくれるから
Because you are right there with me.
君の瞳の中 反射した私を見て
Looking at myself reflected in your eyes,
はじめて自分の色を知れたんだ
For the first time, I came to know my own color.
まだ、満開じゃないけど
Even though it's not in full bloom yet,
鮮やかな夢を映し出せるよ
I can reflect vivid dreams.
この画面いっぱいに 花びらのひとつひとつを
Filling this entire screen, every single petal,
好きになった そこに君が、いつも君がいてくれたから
I grew to love them, because you, always you, were there for me.
la la la…
La la la...
みんな、生誕ライブ見てくれてありがとうございました！
Thank you everyone for watching the birthday live!
ここで告知が3つあります！1つ目はこ・ち・ら！
Now, there are 3 announcements! The first one is... right here!
さくらみこ誕生日記念グッズが出ます！キービジュアルはオルガン先生に描いていただきました！
Sakura Miko's birthday commemorative merchandise is out! The key visual was drawn by Organ-sensei!
イラストのテーマは今回のライブのコンセプトと同じ「さくらのお姫様」です！
The illustration theme is 'Sakura Princess', same as this live's concept!
フルセットはこんな感じになっています！それでは1つずつ見ていきましょう！
The full set looks like this! Let's check them out one by one!
まずはこちら！さくらのお姫様LEDアートパネル！
First is this! Sakura Princess LED art panel!
背景を光らせることができるアートパネルと...
An art panel that can make the background glow and...
さくらのお姫様LEDアートパネルとなっております。
It's the Sakura Princess LED Art Panel.
ドレスをまとって、お姫様になったそのライブでのみこを思い出せるグッズとなっております。
It's merchandise to remind you of Miko as a princess in her dress from that live concert.
次はこちら！
Next is this!
ちびみこ指パペット～巫女衣装＆35P着ぐるみver.～です。
Chibi Miko Finger Puppet ~Shrine Maiden & 3P Costume Ver.~
キーホルダーとしても使える指パペットが登場！
Finger puppets that can also be used as keychain holders are here!
3Pの着ぐるみをつ付けたり外したりもできるので、気分に合わせてカスタマイズしてね。
You can put on or take off the 3P costume, so customize it to match your mood!
次はこちら！
Next is this!
さくらのお姫様 うたた寝ラバーマスコット。
Sakura Princess Naptime Rubber Mascot.
ついうたた寝しちゃったみこをマスコットとして再現しました！
We've recreated Miko dozing off as a mascot!
みんなのおうちでみこがすやすやします。ちっちゃいのでかわいいよ。
Miko will nap cozily in your house. It's small and super cute!
最後はこちら！
Last is this!
35Pふわふわカードホルダー！
3P Fluffy Card Holder!
みこにカードホルダーになってもらいました！
Miko became a card holder for you!
みこのホロカを入れてもよし、特定のちびほうブロマイドカードを入れてもよしの汎用性の高いグッズです。
It's a versatile item that's great for holding Miko's Holoca or special chibi bromides.
そしてそして、フルセット購入特典はこちら！チェキ風ブロマイドカード！
And the full set purchase bonus is right here: Cheki-style bromide cards!
数量限定バージョンにはみこの直筆サインが入ります。
The quantity-limited version includes Miko's handwritten autograph.
通常バージョンにも箔押しのサインが入りますが、直筆質が欲しい方は早めにご購入ください。
The regular version has a foil-stamped signature, but if you want the handwritten one, please purchase early!
22時10分から発売開始となります。よろしくお願いします。
Sales start at 22:10. Thank you for your support!
今回はフルセット購入特典もつきます。
This time, full set purchase bonuses are also included.
特定ボイス、タイトルは「みこのこれから」。
The special voice title is "Miko's Future."
ソロライブを終えたみこが今後についてみこぴーに話すような内容です。
It's a voice drama where Miko talks to Mikopii about the future after her solo live.
ソロライブから今日の3Dライブの間のお話なので、このボイスを聞いた後にもう一回配信を見返すとより心にしみわたるかも？
It's an intimate chat set between the solo live and today's 3D live, so listening to it and rewatching the stream might touch your heart even more!
さらにフルセット特典として、昨年の9月から発売されたホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで使用できるカードが1枚付きます。
Additionally, as a full set bonus, you'll get one PR card usable in the Hololive Official Card Game released last September.
カードはホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップでご購入された方のみ対象となります。
Cards are only eligible for purchases made at the Hololive Production Official Shop.
特典につくのは推しアピールできるキーカード「推し滅面カード」です。
The bonus card is the Oshi-Oshimen Card, which lets you show off your Oshi!
カードの詳細や遊び方についてはホームページにてご確認ください。
Please check the homepage for details and how to play with the cards.
カードは日本語版のみとなりますのでご容赦ください。
Please note that the cards are available in Japanese only.
告知2つ目はこーちら！
The second announcement is right here!
お待たせしました！さくらみこ 1st Live「flower fantasista!」Blu-ray発売決定！やったー！
Thanks for waiting! Sakura Miko 1st Live "flower fantasista!" Blu-ray announced! Yay!
超エリートにさけほこったみこ初めてのソロライブを何度でもで見返せるので、みんな絶対に購入してください！
You can rewatch Miko's very first, ultra-elite solo live as many times as you want, so everyone make sure to buy it!
詳細は後日発表されますのでお楽しみに！
Details will be announced later, so look forward to it!
告知の3つ目はこーちら！
The third announcement is this!
「Re:lection」のMVが公開されます！
The MV for "Re:lection" will be released!
このあとすぐプレミア公開になりますのでお見逃しなく！
It will premiere right after this, so don't miss it!
そしてそして、まだあります。鳴門鯛焼本舗とさくらみこコラボ第3弾が全国49店舗で開催中です！
And furthermore, the 3rd Naruto Taiyaki Honpo collaboration with Sakura Miko is currently being held at 49 stores nationwide!
3月31日までですので、ぜひみんな食べに行ってください！
It runs until March 31st, so please go eat some!
そして、さくらみこショップコラボの喋るエリート加湿器が現在受注販売受付中です！
Also, Sakura Miko's talking elite humidifier is currently accepting pre-orders!
うるさいほどよく喋るので、みんなぜひおうちに置いてね！
It talks loud and clear, so make sure to get one for your home!
詳しくは公式サイトを見てください！
Check the official website for details!
そして、今週末はホロライブ6thフェス「Color Rise Harmony」とエキスポがあります！
And this weekend are the Hololive 6th Fes "Color Rise Harmony" and Expo!
みんな応援よろしくお願いします！
Everyone, your support would be greatly appreciated!
以上、お知らせでした！
That's all for the announcements!
それではですね、このあとメンバー限定で撮影会＆アンコールライブがあるので、みんなさくら組に入ってね！
And now, since there's a membership-exclusive photo session and encore live right after this, everyone join Sakura-gumi!
おつみこでした！バイバーイ！
It was Miko! Bye-bye!
みこの色は みんながおしえてくれたんだよ。
Everyone taught me what Miko's color is.
みんなと見た景色を 何度だって思い出して
Remembering the scenery we shared time and time again,
もっと輝くステージへ！！
toward an even brighter stage!!
ありがとうだよー
Thank you so much!